hukkubandar.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy

The text below shows Privacy Policy for the Apps that you use on hukkubandar.com. This privacy policy sets out how hukkubandar uses and protects any information that you give for hukkubandar Applications when you use them. hukkubandar is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. When we ask you to provide certain information while authenticating the app and issuing certain permission by which you can be identified while using Applications, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

hukkubandar may change this policy from time to time by updating this section. This privacy policy was last updated on 11th Jan 2015. If we make any material changes to our policies, then we will either put message on our website or you need to check this section in order to comply with our policies.

**What Data we collect?**

We may collect the following data from your profile:

We are collecting your basic profile information mainly your facebook profile photo, name, country, location, birthdate, gender.  
We are collecting your private Messages/Inbox Counts.  

**What we do with the Data we collected?**

We require this data to understand your needs and provide you with a good experience while using our Apps, and in particular way for the reasons below:

We use your basic informations to create funny photos which can be download and shared!  
We require your certain information for the application you use to work  
We do not store or view your private Messages  

**How do we protect your information?**

We ensures at it best to keep your information secure. The use of this information is done while processing or using this Apps and which is temporary.

We never get any sensitive details such as passwords.  
We never store any details of facebook users except the Photo Results generated.  

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. None of your informations are stored in our database.   
hukkubandar.com will not be responsible for any illegal activities on facebook. hukkubandar.com never upload any data to facebook. By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**3rd Party Advertisements and their Cookies:**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting link below.

Google ad and content network privacy policy

**Contact:**

If you have any questions regarding privacy policy, abuse, reports or queries please contact us via email at info@hukkubandar.com.  
In case you found any objectionable content on our website, Intellectual Property Violation you should send us email at info@hukkubandar.com before taking any further action. We will be happy in solving your issue.
